novinite.com 2014-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Novinite.com - Sofia News Agency

**Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) takes your privacy extremely seriously.  
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. **

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) treatment of personally identifiable information that the site automatically collects when you are on the Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) site, and when you use other Novinite.com's services. 

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect some anonymous information each time you visit Novinite.com, for statistical purposes, so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience.

We collect personal information from you through: 

  * the use of the registration forms  

  * the forms for sending news to a friend  

  * every time you e-mail us your details  

Once you register with Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) and sign in to our services or you send news to a friend, the information you entered is not anonymous to us. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) staff treats your e-mail address as strictly confidential information. Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency) will NOT sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone in any case and any price and will not use your name and e-mail address for any other purposes than the purposes of the site services. 

The opinions posted on the forum and emails sent to the editor are public and are viewable by anyone on the Internet. This information may be indexed by global Internet search engines (e.g. Google, Yahoo, Altavista, etc.) 

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit Novinite.com (Sofia News Agency). A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

**Security**

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing Novinite.com and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices, please contact us by e-mail [here](http://www.novinite.com/about/contact_us). 

## [Ups & Downs](http://www.novinite.com/view_updown.php?updown_id=371)

Bulgarian Business to Offer Students Summer Jobs

Dozens Unaccounted for After Odessa Clashes

## [Archives](http://www.novinite.com/archives)
